tell me how do you imagine a shared
tomorrow one where your greatest assets
are valued and protected one where your
company's legacy is treasured and
cherished one where the next generation
is hopeful and prepared
but in this bright and beautiful world
there can be bleak and foreboding times
as the things we cannot foresee catch us
off-guard while the matters we overlook
may cost us in the long run we seek
shelter with the favorable and familiar
look upon each other for warmth hold on
the hands of whom we trust for amidst
our differences we are all looking at
the same direction where people our
greatest assets are secure where the
nation your company's legacy is enduring
where our future those next-in-line
stand confident under the care of the
country's first and longest standing
life insurer we can create sustainable
conditions for employees to live
brighter we can build strong
relationships for dependents to thrive
brighter we can harness global
connections for communities to flourish
brighter because when we take care of
people our own people our business and
bottom lines also prosper together we
can cover future needs we can open
opportunities we can build a brighter
Philippines for every Filipino family
now tell me can our share tomorrow shine
even brighter only under the Sun visit
Sun life.com pH today